Eric: Hello. Do you have a room for tonight?
Receptionist: Let’s see. Yes, there’s a room on the second floor.
Louisa: Great. Can we see it?
Receptionist: Of course. Come with me.
Eric: Is there an elevator?
Receptionist: A lift? I’m sorry, no there isn’t.
But I can help you with your cases.
This is the room.
Louisa: Ah, it’s beautiful. I love it!
Eric: Yes, and there’s a great view of Loch Ness.
Is there Wi-Fi?
Receptionist: Yes, there is. The password is ‘Scotland’.
Eric: Is there a restaurant? We’re very hungry.
Receptionist: No, there isn’t a restaurant.
But you can have a sandwich in the bar, or there are some pubs in the village.
Louisa: Are there any shops near here?
Receptionist: No, there aren’t any shops near the hotel.
Eric: OK, thanks. I have one more question.
Receptionist: Yes?
Eric: Is there really a monster in Loch Ness?
Receptionist: Well, some people say there isn’t and some people say there is…
Enjoy your stay. Breakfast is at eight.